*****had been calledarney a loof names over the years.
孩子 这些年你们Barney叔叔 有过很多称呼
Jerk!
混蛋!
Bastard!
贱人!
Barack Obama Jr.
巴拉克 奥巴马二世
And yes... we can.
我们做得到 (奥巴马当选演讲)
But there's one name none of us ever expted to hear him called.
但有一个称呼 我们完全没想到会落在他头上
Boyfriend. Barney Stinson is my boyiend.
男朋友 Barney Stinson是我男朋友
I've said it,like, a hundred times it still sounds weird to say.
我差不多在嘴里念叨了一百次  感觉还是很奇怪
Well,anything sounds weird if you say it a hundred times.
什么东西念叨一百次 都会感觉奇怪
Bowl. Bowl.
碗 碗
Bowl.
碗
- But other than that, things are good? - Bowl.
- 除了这个 其他事还好吧? - 碗
- Bowl. - I don't know.
- 碗 - 我不知道
- I think Barney's been single for too long. - Bowl.
- 我觉得Barney做单身汉太久了 - 碗
- Like,the other night, I wake up at 4:00 a.m.-- - Bowl.
- 有一晚 我半夜4点睡醒 - 碗
Barney,are you awake?
Barney 你醒了吗?
Barney?
Barney. This is not a one-night stand.
Barney 这不是一夜情
Wee dating. Come back to bed.
我们在拍拖 快回来睡
- Bowl. - That's happened three times.
- 碗 - 这种情况发生了三次
And it's not just that, it's other things.
而且不止这些 还有其他
What's wrong?
怎么了?
It was just one thing after another at work today, and then...
今天的工作忙的要命 而且...
I found out my aunt's in the hospital.
我阿姨进了医院
I'm just,I'm feeling so overwhelmed and it's just...
我 我感觉自己不能承受这么多...
What you need to do is talk through this stuff.
你需要把事情都说出来
Ohthanks.
谢谢你
And then,once you're off the phone with Lily, I'll be down in the bar ready to have sex. Mm-kay?
所以咯 你跟Lily挂完电话去酒吧找我 我会准备好跟你嘿咻
Bowl.
碗
Look,I'm not the touchy-feely-est person in the world,but...
我不是那种喜欢整天厮守在一起的人 但是...
- a little more effort would be nice. - Bowl.
- 有一点卿卿我我总是好的 - 碗
- I understand. - Bowl.
- 我了解 - 碗
- I guess,in a lot of ways, Baey doesn't stack up. - Bowl.
- 我想Barney在很多方面还没准备好 - 碗
- I mean,you've had some pretty incredible boyfriends. - Bowl. Bowl.
- 毕竟 你的前任男友都挺出色的 - 碗 碗
Bowl. Bowl.
碗 碗哦~
- No,that's not it. - Bowl
- 不 这个就不咋地 - 碗
I don't know Maybe he just doesn't have it in him.
我不知道 或许他根本就不是那种人
Maybe is whole thing's a big mistake.
或许我们之间根本就是个错误
Bowl?
碗?
- She really said that? - And she meant it. Trust me.
- 她真的这么说? - 她是认真的 相信我
I dated Robin for a year-- if you don't nt to lose her, you gotta try a little harder.
我跟Robin拍拖一年 如果你不想失去她 你得努力点
Be more attentive to where she is emotionally.
在她有心事时多点关心她
You know,just be present.
让她感受到你的存在
- Yes,totally. - Yeah.
- 对哦 - 当然
Only thing, and this is st me-- I like my testicles attached to my body,
不过呢 我这个人呢 与其让雄风消逝在Robin的包包里
rather than rolling around next to some eyeliner in Robin's purse. Stinson out!
我宁愿把它留在身边长存不灭  Stinson不玩了!
But then a funny thing happened.
接着有趣的事发生了
Over the next couple weeks, Barney was thoughtful, considerate...
接下来的几周 Barney既体贴 又周到...
sweet.
非常甜蜜
In short, the perfect boyfriend.
总而言之 是一个完美的男友
Which,to Robin, meant only one thing.
对Robin而言 这意味着一件事
- He's cheating on me. - What?
- 他在偷腥 - 啥?
Why else would he buy me flowers? He's gettin' some on the side.
不然他怎么会给我买花? 他有小三了
Oh,come on,Robin.
别这样 Robin
Barney's not the type of guy who would... Go on.
Barney不是那种会... 继续
Plus,he keeps saying he's working le.
还有 他一直说他工作很忙
But when I call his office, they say he ft hours ago.
但我打给他公司  他们说他一个小时前就走了
- Well,that doesn't prove anything. - Yes. Proof. Go word.
- 那不能证明什么呀 - 没错 证明 好词儿
I'm glad you brought that up.
既然你提起
Barney's briefcase. He forgot it here this morning.
这是Barney的公文包 今早他落在这了
And what dyou plan on doing with it?
那你准备干嘛?
We,we-- you and I-- are going to open it up and look for evidence.
是我们 你和我哦 准备把它打开  寻找证据
- Ted probably has a slgehammer around here somewhere. - No! Stop! Stop!
- 我记得Ted有个锤子在这里 - 别! 别!
Eye contact. Lien to me.
看着我 听我说
Robin Scherbatsky is many things: friend,confidant,
Robin Scherbatsky在我的眼中 是挚友 知己
occasional guest star in some confusing dreams that remind me a woman's sexuality is a moving target.
有时会客串在某些可疑的梦中  迷乱了我的性取向
But she is no crazy, jealous stalker-bitch. Let go.
但绝对不是善妒 高傲的疯婆娘 放手
Hey,I've been down in the basement storage area going through all the stuff
嘿 我在地下贮藏室整理Lily和我
that Lily and I left behind when we moved out.
搬走时留下的东西
I'm sorry Robin. We should've cleared it out for you much sooner.
对不起Robin 我们应该早腾出来让给你的
There's a basement storage area?
有个地下贮藏室?
Oh,you're not upset. Good.
你没生气 太好了
Baby, guess what I found.
宝贝 看我找到了什么
- Oh,that's great,honey. - What the hell is that?
- 太好了 亲爱的 - 那是什么东东啊?
Marshall got it in college.
Marshall读大学时留下来的
He used it as a nightstand for years.
这些年他用来做床头几
Until we found out that Lily was allergic to barrel resin
后来我们发现Lily对木桶树脂过敏
- Barrel resin? - Just go with it.
- 木桶树脂? - 别深究哦
So you need a hand throwing it out?
需要帮忙扔掉吗?
No,I'm not... I'm not just going to throw her outokay?
不 我才...我才不会把它扔掉呢
Mabel's like family.
Mabel是我的家人
So,um,what are you going to do withabel?
那你要拿Mabel怎么办?
I want to give her away, um,to a lucky new owner. Do you know anyone?
我要把她托付给一处好人家  你有好介绍吗?
Yeah,hmm,let me think. Do I know any rodeo clowns?
嗯 我想想哈 我认识哪个斗牛士保护者呢? (化小丑妆 在斗牛士受伤时吸引牛注意的人)
Oh,that's weird,I do.
真奇怪 我认识耶
But even Lenny wouldn't go near that mess.
不过我想Lenny也不想碰那麻烦
Well,'s not going to have the chance, because I am putting old Mabel in the Bermuda Triangle.
他没机会了  因为我要把Mabel放在百慕大三角洲里
"The rmuda Triangle" was the name we'd given years earlier to the curb right in front of our building.
"百慕大三角洲" 是几年前我们 给公寓门前的那段路起的名字
Whenever we wanted to give something away, we'd put it right there.
当我们要处理掉什么东西  就把它放在那里
It was uncanny.
真的很离奇
This is so exciting.
这真的太让人兴奋了
Right now there's some out there who has no idea that tonight they're going home with just...
外头的某个陌生人  今晚正要与最好的木桶...
just the best barrel.
一起回家
Well,let's just hope they're not allergic to barrel sin like Lily here.
希望他们不会像Lily那样 对木桶树脂过敏吧
Be cool,by. Damn!
要低调 靠!
- See you,sweetie. Good luck. - Bye,abe.
- 掰了 亲爱的 好运呐 - 再见 宝贝
- Now,can we plea get out of here? - Yeah. I'll grab my coat.
- 咱们快离开这好吗? - 好啦 我去拿外套
A college notebook?
大学笔记本?
Oh,my God, he's cheating on me with some college girl.
天 他背着我钓了一个大学妞
I knew there was a skank but I thought she'd at least be dumb.
我就知道有奸情吧 但是我以为他一定钓了个傻女孩
"Birthday: July 23. "Favote hockey team: the Vancouver Canucks.
"生日 7月23日" "最喜欢的冰球队: 温哥华加人队"
Age:29,but tells people that she's 26."
"年龄:29岁 对外宣称26岁"
Oh,my God, these are notes about me.
天 这本笔记本写的是我
Or some 29-year-old versioof me.
或者是29岁的我
I hope I'm not too late!
希望还赶得及!
I want to see the look of joy on the new owner's face!
我想看到捡到她的人脸上的喜悦!
She's still there!
她还在那儿!
Okay Mabel,let's find you a new home.
Mabel 一起找处好人家吧
Here comes a guy! And he...
有个男人过来了! 他...
he just walked, lked right on by it.
他径自走过
He's probably rushing home to get a handcart or something. Yeah!
可能他想赶回家拿手推车还是什么
Hey,better hurry up,pal.
嘿 兄弟你最好快点哦
What are you guys doing with Barney's secret Robin notebook?
你们拿着Barney的Robin秘密笔记本干嘛?
Let me rephrase that.
我重新再说一遍
Did you two ladies se some weight?
你们俩好像瘦了点哦?
What do you know about th,Marshall?
你知道点什么? Marshall
Why woulBarney have a notebook full of information about me?
为什么Barney会有一本关于我的笔记本?
Well...
呃...
The truth was...
事实上...
Barney was taking a night school class taught... by me.
Barney正在上夜校 由我...开课
Welcome to Robin 101.
欢迎来到Robin 101
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=- proudly presents
-=伊甸园美剧论坛 http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=- sync:咔肉肉
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: HOLAH 狗灯儿 校对: 葱家的小毛毛 时间轴: 咔肉肉
How I Met Your Mother Season05 Episode03
老爸老妈浪漫史 第五季 第三集
Why is Ted teaching a class about me?
为什么Ted会开一门关于我的课?
It all started a few weeks ag ...
一切要从几周前说起...
rather than rolling around next to some eyeliner in Robin's purse.
我宁愿把它留在身边长存不灭
Stinson out!
Stinson不玩了!
Stinson back in.
Stinson又回来了
Say,hypothetically, did want to change who I am to become a better boyfriend to Robin,
假设 我想变成Robin希望的那种好男友
which I do not!
当然我不会!
What kind of changes are we talking about?
我需要改变什么?
Why,I mean, there's just so much you need to know about her.
那 对她 你需要太多的了解了
Okay,for starters, don't ever cry in front her.
好 初学者须知 永远不要在她面前哭
Okay
好
And whatever you do, don't cry in front of her four times.
还有不管怎样 别在她面前哭四次
Hey,guys. What you talking abo?
嘿 说啥呢?
- Fantasy football. - Fantasy football.
- 梦幻橄榄球 - 梦幻橄榄球
They realized they couldn't talk about this stuff at the b,
他们发现这不能在吧里讨论
and since you live with Ted, they had to find someplace safe. So...
而且因为你跟Ted一起住  所以他们得找个安全的地方 那就是...
Ted's classroom.
Ted的教室
"How To Date Robin Scherbatsky." Lesson one.
"如何跟Robin Scherbatsky拍拖"  第一课
Now,even ough she puts up a tough exterior, what Robin really wants, deep down...
尽管她表现得很高傲 但Robin真正想要的 内心深处的...
I'm bored.
好无聊
You said you wanted my help.
你说过想要我帮忙的
Can we draw boobs on the chalkboard?
能在黑板上画对咪咪吗?
We did that ready.
已经画过了
- No,like,really big boobs. - No.
- 不 是那种大咪咪 - 不行
Look,I need this,too.
我也需要你的帮忙
I've only been a professor a few weeks.
我成为教授不过几周
Being up here,it's, it's good practice for me.
给你上课 对我来说是个很好的锻炼
- Can we have class outside? - No!
- 咱们能来个户外教学吗? - 不行!
What Rob really wants deep down...
Robin内心深处真正想要的...
- Barney! - What?
- Barney! - 干嘛?
I'm tweeting about you. You should be flattered.
我在Twitter上更新你的信息呢 你该很荣幸了
How do you spell blah-bh-blah-- "H's" or no?
"废话连篇"怎么打 "bian"还是"pian"?
Wow,you were just, like,the worst student in the world,weren't you?
你还真是个坏学生啊
They said I had A-D... something. Can we havclass outside?
他们说我有A.D... 啥的 （多动症） 咱们能来个户外教学吗?
Barney,I'm only gonna say th once, so lisn up.
Barney 我只说一次 听好了
I love you and I love bin.
我爱你 我也爱Robin
And I want to make this work.
我希望你们好
So if you give me a few weeks of attention, I coulgive you a lifetime of happiness.
如果你给我几周的专注力  我会回报你一辈子的幸福
Can you do that for me?
为了我 你能做到吗?
Do you tnk I should get Sports Illustrated for 70% off the cover price?
"体育画报"打三折 你觉得我应该买吗?
Can we have class outside?
咱们能来个户外教学吗?
I got to find a way to reach ts kid.
我一定要搞定这倒霉孩子
"Class numb two."
"第二课"
"Top Ten Robin Scherbatsk Facial Expressions And Their Meaning."
"Robin Scherbatsk十大面部表情 与其意义"
Now,notice the vacant eyes, the pa,queasy expression, suggesting nausea.
留意这混沌的眼神 苍白的脸色  一脸的反胃状
- What do these mean? - You guys just had sex?
- 是什么意思? - 你们俩刚嘿咻完?
- Wasn't me. - Dude!
- 不是我说的 - 伙计!
I worked reallhard on these slides,okay? Can we just...
这些幻灯片我花了很大功夫 能不能...
Okay.
好
This look is hunger.
这是饥饿的表情
If you ever see Robin looking like this, get some food in her quick, one of two things will happen.
要是你见到这种表情 赶紧给她弄点吃的 不然有两种情况会发生
One: weird,out-of-context laughter
第一:奇怪 无厘头的大笑
Or two: spontaneously falling leep in strange places.
第二:不自觉地在陌生的地方睡着
But the most important facial expreson of all?
但是 最重要的面部表情是?
That's a building.
那是一栋建筑物
That's for my class. The Flatiron Building.
这是我的课的幻灯片 熨斗型建筑
Fun story about it.
有段故事很有趣
It was designed by Chicago's Daniel Burnham in the beaux arts style;
这是芝加哥的Daniel Burnham 以美术风格设计的
- this architectural gem - Dude
- 这个建筑学的珍宝 - 伙计
Right. The most importa facial expression of all.
对 最重要的面部表情是
Flar nostril ridges.
张开的鼻翼
Wide,unblinking eyes.
圆睁的双眼
If you ever, ever see this face,Barney, run.
要是看到了这个表情 Barney 快跑
And don't take a picture of it.
记住 别拍照
She will punch you.
她会揍你的
And you will cry...
而你会哭...
for the third time... that night.
那晚上...都哭了三次了
Which brings us to an important point: defusing the bomb.
所以得出重要结论 千万不能让她爆发
"Defusing the bomb"? What does that even mean?
别让我爆发?这算什么嘛?
"Three Topics To Distract Robin From Being Mad At You."
"避免Robin生你气的三个方法"
"Distract" me? Oh,that is so condescending.
避免我生气? 好像我很容易生气一样
These guys are really starting to piss me off!
这两家伙气死老娘了!
"Immediately switch the conversation to one of the following,
"赶紧切换以下几种话题
"unless you want bin to start throwing her shoes."
可以避免Robin生气的时候乱丢鞋子..."
One. "Vancouver Canucks 2004 Division Title."
第一个 "温哥华加人队夺得2004年度分赛区冠军"
What? That's not distracting.
什么? 这算什么转移话题
That's just talking about the story a scrappy little underdog team
我不过是说说一个落魄低迷的球队
that prevailed despite very shaky goaending and,frankly,the decling skills of Trevor Linden.
如何在还有个差劲的守门员 而且Trevor Linden的状态还每况愈下 的情况下获得了最终的胜利
Two: "Proper Gunleaning and Maintenance."
第二  "正确的枪支清洁保养法"
You have to clean your gun My uncle had a filthy old shotgun,
清洁枪支是必须的 我叔叔的枪就特别不干净
blew both his thumbs off trying to shoot a beaver.
某次想打水懒的时候 倒把自己的俩大拇指打掉了
You want to distract someone, make them watch my uncle try to eat corn on the cob.
想别让人家生气 去看我叔叔没有拇指怎么吃玉米吧
Three: "Emperor Penguins."
第三 "帝企鹅"
Did you know that before intercourse, the male and female emperor penguins bow to each other?
你知道吗 在交配之前 雌雄帝企鹅会向彼此行礼的
Mr. Penguin. Mrs. Penguin.
企鹅先生好 企鹅女士好
Oh,God,silly penguins, acting all fancy.
好玩吧 蠢蠢的企鹅 还要装优雅
What were we talking about?
你刚才在说什么来着?
Looks like we got a taker.
有人想要了
Oh,come on,dude.
来吧 伙计
You know you want to A guy like you, beard,no mustache.
像你这样络腮胡而不留八字胡的人
You're exactly the kind of guy who could use a sweet barrel.
这样的可爱小木桶最适合你了
Do it.
拿走吧
No. That's not a fire hydrant! What...
晕 这又不是消防栓! 搞什么...
For shame,ir. For shame!
你真可耻 真是可耻!
I bet you couldn't even grow a mustache if you wanted to.
我打赌你这样的 就算想长八字胡都长不出来
Neither can you,sweetie.
亲爱的 你也长不了啊
ll,he doesn't know that,baby! God!
但是他不知道啊 亲爱的! 真是的!
Ted's only teaching Barney horrible things about me.
Ted一直在跟Barney说我坏话
I don't know. Check this out.
不是哦 看这个
This is actually kind of sweet.
这个蛮可爱的哦
Now,we alknow Robin's not what you'd call "touchy-feely."
现在我们已经知道Robin 不是那种整日痴缠的类型
She doesn't say,"I love you," like a normal person.
她也不会像普通人一样说 我爱你
Instead,she'll laugh, shake her head, give you a little smile and say,"You're an idiot."
相反的 她会哈哈大笑 摇头晃脑 冲你微微笑 说“你个傻瓜”
- "You're an idiot"? - Yup.
- "你个傻瓜"? - 对
If sheells you you're an idiot,you're a lucky man.
如果她说你是傻瓜 那你就俘获她的心了
And if she does say "I loveou," she's already broken up with you in her mind.
如果她真跟你说 我爱你 那她在心底里其实已经不喜欢你了
I think 's nice that Ted knows you that well.
Ted这么了解你 真是厉害啊
ah,well,too bad it's next to a page entitled...
恶心的是 下一页讲的是...
"bin Scherbatsky's Surprising Erogenous Zones."
"Robin Scherbatsky的情欲敏感点"
Right knee-- ticklish.
右膝盖 怕痒
Left knee...
左膝盖...
Does lefty like that?
左边这样摸爽不爽?
Oh,yeah... lefty like that.
欧也... 左边超爽
I can't believe I'm taking sexual advice from Ted Mosby.
真不想相信我居然向Ted Mosby 请教房事秘籍
That's like taking fashion advice from...
就感觉是向Ted Mosby...
well,Ted Mosby.
请教穿衣风潮一样
Oh,here's a good one.
这个好玩
"Top Five Things Never to Do Around Robin."
"不能在Robin身边做的五件事"
Three: "Never,ever play the 'Guess Who' game with her."
第三 "千万别蒙她眼 玩猜猜我是谁的游戏"
What do you mean?
这话啥意思?
Gueswho?
猜猜我是谁?
It's me! It's me! It's me!
是我! 是我! 是我!
Number four: "Unless you want to seit 80 times a day, for the next month,
第四: "千万别让Robin看youtube上的 小动物玩乐器的视频
never show Robin a YouTube clip of an animal playing a musical instrument."
看了以后 她会不停的重复做给你看"
Barney!
Do you have a problem with this class?
你不喜欢这个课吗?
Yeah,it's boring asell and I'm not learning anything.
当然是 无聊要死了 啥也没学到
Uh,well,maybe the problem is your attude.
那是因为你学习态度不端正
You're not listening to a word I say.
从来不认真听课
Uh,can you hear this,Professor?
那你明白这个了没有 教授?
Or should I turn it up for you?
或许你要我转手向上才明白?
It may not have been a thumbs-up,kids.
孩子们 或许不是大拇指向上吧 （应该是竖了中指）
,you think you're not learning anything,huh?
你觉得你啥也没学到 对吧?
- Okay. Poquiz. - What...
- 好的 随堂测验 - 什么...
When Robin's PMS-ing,at kind of chocolate should you get her?
Robin大姨妈来的时候 要给她买什么巧克力?
Trick question. Get her butterscotch.
脑筋急转弯啊 应该买奶油糖果
Correct! Why?
正确!为什么?
Butterscotch is to Canadian women what chocolate is to American women.
奶油糖果对加拿大女性的重要性 犹如巧克力对美国女性一样重要
Correct!
正确!
What is Robin's dream job?
Robin一直梦想成为?
To become the most successful female TV journalistof all time.
成为世界上最有名的电视女主播
Correct! And if she achieves that,will she truly be happy?
正确!如果她真的做到了 她会不会开心呢?
No! Robin's deep-seated need for attention can traced back to her father's emotional distance,
不会! Robin内心想得到别人的关注 是因为小时候老爸的漠不关心
and no aunt of success will ever make up for what she truly needs,
无论多么事业成功 都不能满足她真实所需
which is six si from her Dad: "Robin, I'm proud of y,eh?"
那就是她爸爸对她说 "Robin 我以你为傲"
Yes!
答对了!
But I guess you're right.
你说的对
You haven't learned anything.
你什么也没学到
Sorry to have wasted your time.
浪费你时间了 不好意思
"O Captain! My Captain!"
"噢 船长! 我的船长!" (惠特曼的诗歌 也出现在死亡诗社电影中)
How good was Dead Poet's Society?
死亡诗社那电影真是不错哈?
I know,right? The end? Tears.
可不是 那结尾 超感人啊
Okay,can I just say that my deepest need in life not to have my father to say,"I am proud of you,eh?"
好吧 请容我辩解一下 我最需要的 不是我爸爸对我说"我以你为傲"
*****
那你现在干嘛要哭
- I'm not crying. - Oh,sweetie.
- 我没哭 - 宝贝过来抱抱
Can I get you me butterscotch?
要不要来点奶油糖果?
Oh,stop it.
不用了
Wait a second. It says here that the class meets at 6:15 on Tuesday.
等等 上面写周二六点一刻要上课
- So? - That's right now.
- 所以? - 就是现在咯
Now,as you can e, well over 50% of the blankets have been dragged onto her side.
正如你所见 超过50%的毛巾毯 都被她扯过去了
Make no mistake.
千万别记错
Robin Scherbatsky is a classic,textbook...
Robin Scherbatsky是一个典型的教科书式的...
cover hog.
cover hog（一只盖被子的动画猪）
- Any questions? - Yeah,I have one.
- 有什么疑问吗? - 是的 我要提问
Yes,Robin?
好的 Robin你说?
Flared nostril ridges. Wide,unblinking eyes.
张开的鼻翼 圆睁的双眼
I got th. So,emperor penguins-- crazy,huh?
我有办法 帝企鹅超囧的吧?
What the hell do youwo think you're doing?
你俩在搞什么鬼?
Marshall,did you sells out?
Marshall 你是不是出卖我们?
*****I said good-byto a very dear friend today.
我那时非常心碎 我跟一个老朋友告别了
Dude,it's a barrel!
老大 不过是个木桶!
You're giving Mabel away?
你要把Mabel送走了?
I have so many questions. Why would you do this? What weryou thinking?
问题现在是我来问 你干嘛要这样做? 你们脑子进水了?
Who the hell is that guy?
这家伙又是谁?
Oh,that's Shin-Ya. He's sort of been auditing the cla.
他是真矢 他是旁听的
"Auditing"?
"旁听"?
Well,tried to explain to him it wasn't a real class, but I don't think he speaks much English.
我跟他说了这不是常规课程 但是好像他英语不咋地
On the bright side,he came in handy standing in for you during the role-playing exercis.
他来了也有好处 角色扮演的时候 他可以随叫随到啊
Wait. You did role-playing exercises where I was played by Shin-Ya?
等等 你们还来角色扮演 你们叫真矢 来扮演我?
********
他们逼我戴假发
***********
真是太有失身份了
You know, I can't believe you,Ted.
真不敢相信 Ted
You actuallyhink you're some kind of an expert on me?
你真的认为你对我了如指掌?
He is an expert. He's a great teacher!
他的确对你了如指掌 这个老师超赞!
Kiss ass.
拍马屁
You know,half the stuff in this notebook is patently wrong.
这本书里一半都是扯淡
Uh,really? Name one wrong thing.
真的? 举例子看看
"Robin Scherbatsky's Surprising Erogenous Zones"?
"Robin Scherbatsky的情欲敏感地带"?
Let me clear sometng up for you,Ted.
我来跟你澄清一下 Ted
Does lefty like that?
左边爽不爽的?
Yeah...
爽啊...
****
那我们来爽一下右边
Um,the right one's ticklish,I guess.
右边的痒痒
Buthe left one,yeah, I'm glad you're back there.
但是左边就 哦哟 摸回来了好爽哦
Because that is just some sweet,sweet lovin'.
感觉真是妙极了
Noted.
记住了
That was a lie?
你骗我的?
We had just started dating. I was being nice.
我们才刚开始 我不过是为了讨你喜欢
And you.
你得意什么
You know, I got it into my head this week that you were eating on me.
你搞得我以为你在外面有了别的女人
I even broke open your briefcase to look for evidence.
我甚至拆了你的皮包来找证据的
That is a huge violation of my privacy!
你这是窥探我的隐私!
- Go on. - You know,in a way, I was right.
- 继续说 - 从某方面来说 我想的对
You cheated. You can't get some crib sheet on dating me.
你是在骗我  按照这些条条框框来追我是不可能的
That's not how it works.
哪有这样追女孩的
If we n't figure out how to be with each other in aeal,honest way,
如果我们不能坦诚相待 真实面对
I don't see the point of even trying.
在一起也没有什么意思了
*******
如果你俩玩完了 我能去追她不
What do you want?
你想干嘛?
Look. All that stuff I told Barney...
我告诉Barney的所有事...
It was personal between you and me. I'm really sor.
本来应该是我俩的秘密 真抱歉
I guess I'm impressed by how much you remembered.
不过你居然都还记得 我很感动
It's funny.
真好玩
When you date someone,it's like you're taking one long course in
当你在跟别人谈恋爱的时候 就好比在上一节长长的课
who that person is and then,when you break up,
来了解她的为人 而当你跟她分手以后
all that stuff becomes useless.
所学的东西却都完全无用了
It's the emotionalquivalent of an English degree.
相当于英语学位的情感版
I guess I just liked thedea of putting all my Robin Scherbatsky knowledge to good use,you know?
我想我不过是想把我所知的 Robin Scherbatsky都学有所用 对吧?
Well,since you kn me pretty well...
既然你这么了解我...
am I fooling myself with this whole Barney thing?
那我是不是在骗自己 和Barney真的可以在一起?
I don't ow.
不知道
I will say this,though.
但是我能告诉你
I've seen Barney work veryard to get women.
我见过Barney费尽心思去追女孩子
I've seen him work very hard to get rid of women.
也见过他费尽心思摆脱女人
I've ner seen him work this hard to keep one around.
我却从来没有见过他为了 留住谁而如此费心
I was going to give him an A.
我本来要给他个A的
Well,B+ -- Shin-Ya kind of screwed up the curve.
其实是B+  真矢的角色扮演不够到位
Before you say anything, I am done with this stupid Robin 101,okay?
在你生气之前我说一句 我已经不去上那个Robin101了 好吗?
Here,I'll get rid of the notebook.
你看 我现在就丢了这个笔记本
But there's... there's something that I did want to y to you.
但是... 我要告诉你
Robin,I have been with a lot of women-- blondes,brunettes,redheads;
Robin 我钓过很多女人 金发的 黑发的 红发的
big boobs,small boobs,medium boobs;
大咪咪 小咪咪 中等咪咪的
some boobs that were big, but kind of in a bad way.
还有些太大 大得有点过分的
The point is-- boobs that pointed in opposite rec-- ...
关键是 咪咪方向不对了 关键是...
I'm really scared that you're going to dump me and at's why I did this and I'm sorry.
我害怕你会甩了我 所以我才会这么做的 对不起
You're an idiot.
你个傻瓜
You know...
知道不...
That notebook,um,does contain a lot of personal info, and I think it has my home address.
那个笔记本里面有我的很多私人信息 比如我家的住址
And your work address.
还有你上班的地方
Hey,guys! If you don't want the barrel, can you sit somewhere else?
嘿 伙计们 如果你们不想要木桶 就坐到别的地方去?
******
你们把本来想要木桶的人都吓跑了
Designed by Chicago's Daniel Burnham in the beaux arts style,
由芝加哥的Daniel Burnham 以艺术的手法设计而成
this architecturalem was the first of its kind...
这间建筑艺术瑰宝是第一个...
Uh,Professor Mosby?
Mosby教授?
Yes,Susan?
什么事 Susan?
That's a woman drinking beer on the toilet.
图上是一个女的在马桶上喝酒
Right. That-That... was Daniel Burnham's wife.
对了 这个就是... 就是 Daniel Burnham的妻子
She was a troubled, troubled woman. We are moving on.
她一直都是这样疯狂野蛮的 我们继续下面一页
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=- proudly presents
--------------------------  本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用  禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负  --------------------------